Guide to the Time Inc. Time Research Center Files 1919-2015 MS 3009-RG 13
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Bio Files, 1919-2015; 390.66 Linear feet (391 boxes)
  - -W-
    - Wilson, Gary, 1966-1990 (Offsite-box 1878, Folder 4)
    - Wilson, George Allison, 1936-1953 (Offsite-box 1878, Folder 5)
    - Wilson, Harold, 1964-1987 (Offsite-box 1878, Folder 6-15)
    - Wilson, Harold, 1947-1963 (Offsite-box 1879, Folder 1-3)
    - Wilson, James Q., 1963-1985 (Offsite-box 1879, Folder 4)
    - Wilson, Malcolm, 1973-1980 (Offsite-box 1879, Folder 5)
    - Wilson, Margaret Bush, 1976-1991 (Offsite-box 1879, Folder 6)
    - Wilson, Pete, 1977-1991 (Offsite-box 1879, Folder 7)
    - Wilson, Peter Cecil, 1963-1986 (Offsite-box 1879, Folder 8)
    - Wilson, Robert W., 1965-1990 (Offsite-box 1879, Folder 9)
    - Wilson, Samuel Davis, 1936-1989 (Offsite-box 1879, Folder 10)
    - Wilson, Sloan, 1955-1976 (Offsite-box 1879, Folder 11)
    - Wilson, William A., 1981-1992 (Offsite-box 1879, Folder 12)
    - Wilson, William Julius, 1978-1992 (Offsite-box 1879, Folder 13)
    - Winchell, Walter, 1932-1967 (Offsite-box 1879, Folder 14)
    - Wittegenstein, Ludwig, 1954-1993 (Offsite-box 1879, Folder 15-16)
    - Wood, Grant, 1933-1989 (Offsite-box 1879, Folder 17-18)
  - -X-Y-Z-
    - Yablonski, Joseph A., 1964-1974 (Offsite-box 1880, Folder 1-3)
    - Yadin, Yigael, 1948-1984 (Offsite-box 1880, Folder 4-6)
    - Yamamoto, Isoroku, 1941-1993 (Offsite-box 1880, Folder 7)
    - Yamani, Ahmed Zaki, 1978-1990 (Offsite-box 1880, Folder 8-14)
    - Yamani, Ahmed Zaki, 1967-1977 (Offsite-box 1881, Folder 1-6)
    - Yamasaki, Minoru, 1959-1986 (Offsite-box 1881, Folder 7-10)
    - Yankelovich, Daniel, 1960-1993 (Offsite-box 1881, Folder 11-13)
    - Yeltsin, Boris N., 1993 (Offsite-box 1881, Folder 14-16)
    - Yeltsin, Boris N., 1992 (Offsite-box 1882)
    - Yeltsin, Boris N., 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 1883)
    - Yeltsin, Boris N., 1985-1993 (Offsite-box 1884, Folder 1-6)
    - Yevtushenko, Yevgeny, 1963-1993 (Offsite-box 1884, Folder 7-15)
    - Yevtushenko, Yevgeny, 1961-1986 (Offsite-box 1885, Folder 1-2)
    - Yorkshire Ripper, 1979-1981 (Offsite-box 1885, Folder 3)
    - Yoshida, Shigeru, 1935-1980 (Offsite-box 1885, Folder 4-9)
    - Young family, 1930-1987 (Offsite-box 1885, Folder 10)
    - Young, Andrew J., 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 1885, Folder 11-20)
    - Young, Andrew J., 1962-1991 (Offsite-box 1886, Folder 1-10)
    - Young, Coleman A., 1976-1992 (Offsite-box 1886, Folder 11-15)
    - Young, Coleman A., 1973-1993 (Offsite-box 1887, Folder 1-3)
    - Young, John Watts, 1962-1986 (Offsite-box 1887, Folder 4-8)
    - Zaccaro, John A., 1973-1984 (Offsite-box 1887, Folder 9)
    - Zapata, Emiliano, 1933-1992 (Offsite-box 1887, Folder 10)
    - Zardari, Asif Ali, 1987-1993 (Offsite-box 1887, Folder 11)
    - Zhao, Ziyang, 1988-1993 (Offsite-box 1887, Folder 12-16)
    - Zhao, Ziyang, 1975-1993 (Offsite-box 1888, Folder 1-9)
    - Zhivkov, Todor, 1962-1993 (Offsite-box 1888, Folder 10-15)
    - Zhou, Enlai, 1974-1976 (Offsite-box 1888, Folder 16-18)
    - Zhou, Enlai, 1965-1973 (Offsite-box 1932)
    - Zhou, Enlai, 1937-1992 (Offsite-box 1933)
    - Zhou, Enlai, 1937-1978 (Offsite-box 1934, Folder 1-12)
    - Zumwalt, Elmo R., Jr., 1973-1991 (Offsite-box 1934, Folder 12-14)
    - Zumwalt, Elmo R., Jr., 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 1935, Folder 1-7)
    - Zworykin, Vladimir Kosma, 1935-1982 (Offsite-box 1935, Folder 8)
- Series II. Presidents Files, 1923-1994; 416.34 Linear feet (417 boxes)
  The Presidents Files, called Presidential Files by Time Inc., contain research materials regarding United States presidents used by reporters and researchers at various magazines across Time Inc. While a wide range of materials were collected, many of the items focus on important events that the president attended, any honors the president received prior to or during their presidency, domestic and foreign policies of an administration, public appearances and statements made by the president, White House staffing decisions, the finances of the incoming president, recreational activities that the president enjoyed, and details about their family.
  Materials related to a specific president and a specific subject are in files that include the president's name and a subject as part of the titles. Subjects frequently collected include administration, advisers and assistants, appointments, awards and honors, cabinet, cartoons, congress, correspondence, domestic affairs, family, finances, foreign relations, inauguration, politics, polls, press relations, recreation, speeches, travel, and welfare. Files titled "Sketches" includes general material or biographical details or essays about the president and not drawings. Duplicates of items can be found in different folders for a president if the item relates to more than one topic.
  The majority of materials are magazine and newspaper clippings. Other types of material include article correction forms, telegrams, correspondent dispatches, correspondence between reporters as well as correspondence with White House press representatives, transcripts of interviews and speeches, editorial outlines for articles, editorial policies, press releases, event schedules and programs, event invite lists, lists of White House staff, campaign pamphlets, biographical overviews, drafts of articles, academic papers and articles about the president and his policies, and financial reports.
  According to the storage facility used by Time Inc., one box of John F. Kennedy files spanning from "Powers and Duties" to "Quotes" was destroyed in a flood.
  Based on the original schema, the materials within the Presidents Files are organized chronologically by presidential term and titled with the president's name starting with George Washington and ending with Bill Clinton. Not all presidents are represented within the files. Within each president, files are further organized alphabetically by subject with general files at the front.
  - Washington, George: Sketches, 1962-1979 (Offsite-box 806, Folder 1-16)
    The 1977-1979 folder contains correspondence related to the posthumous promotion of President George Washington to position of General of the Armies of the United States as well as correspondence related to the discovery of letters sent by President Washington to General Thomas Gage, the Commander-in-Chief of the British Armies in North America from 1763 to 1775.
  - Washington, George: Sketches, 1930-1961 (Offsite-box 807, Folder 1-9)
  - Adams, Abigail (née Abigail Smith), 1965-1992 (Offsite-box 1920, Folder 1)
  - Adams Family, 1930-1992 (Offsite-box 1920, Folder 2-6)
    While these folders contain material on the families of the presidents, materials are also on Adamses that may not be relations.
  - Adams, John: Sketches, 1930-1993 (Offsite-box 1920, Folder 7-12)
  - Jefferson, Thomas: Sketches, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 1534, Folder 1)
  - Jefferson, Thomas: Sketches, 1969-1984 (Offsite-box 807, Folder 10-15)
  - Jefferson, Thomas: Sketches, 1925-1968 (Offsite-box 808, Folder 1-9)
  - Madison, James: Sketches, 1992-1993, undated (Offsite-box 808, Folder 10)
  - Madison, James: Sketches, 1931-1991 (Offsite-box 1534, Folder 2-4)
  - Madison Family, 1954-1955, 1961, 1969, 1977, 1985, undated (Offsite-box 808, Folder 11)
  - Monroe, James: Sketches, 1930-1991, undated (Offsite-box 1534, Folder 5-6)
  - Adams, John Quincy: Sketches, 1932-1989 (Offsite-box 1920, Folder 13-15)
  - Jackson, Andrew: Sketches, 1927-1993, undated (Offsite-box 1534, Folder 7-11)
  - Jackson, Mrs. Andrew (née Rachel Donelson), 1925, 1934, 1941-1943, 1951-1953, 1960-1967, 1975-1981, undated (Offsite-box 808, Folder 12)
  - Van Buren, Martin, 1931-1940, 1946-1988, undated (Offsite-box 809, Folder 1)
  - Harrison, William Henry, 1936-1940, 1952-1967, 1974-1993, undated (Offsite-box 809, Folder 2)
  - Tyler, John, 1931-1942, 1954-1970, 1977-1983, 1987, undated (Offsite-box 809, Folder 3)
  - Taylor, Zachary, 1934-1952, 1959-1980, 1991-1992, undated (Offsite-box 809, Folder 4)
  - Fillmore, Mrs. Millard (née Abigal Powers), 1960, 1968, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 809, Folder 5)
  - Fillmore, Millard, 1933-1991, undated (Offsite-box 809, Folder 6)
  - Buchanan, James, 1927-1945, 1954-1981, 1988-1993, undated (Offsite-box 809, Folder 7)
  - Lincoln Family, 1929-1978, 1984-1993, undated (Offsite-box 946, Folder 1-2)
  - Lincoln, Abraham: Sketches [RESTRICTED FOR PRESERVATION], undated (Offsite-box R22)
  - Lincoln, Abraham: Sketches, 1967-1992 (Offsite-box 946, Folder 3-16)
  - Lincoln, Abraham: Sketches, 1963-1966 (Offsite-box 809, Folder 8-17)
  - Lincoln, Abraham: Sketches, 1947-1963 (Offsite-box 810, Folder 1-14)
  - Lincoln, Abraham: Sketches, 1938-1948 (Offsite-box 811, Folder 1-3)
  - Lincoln, Abraham: Sketches, 1929-1937 (Offsite-box 947, Folder 1-3)
  - Lincoln, Abraham: Speeches, 1962-1978, 1985-1992 (Offsite-box 947, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Andrew: Sketches, 1931-1942, 1948-1974 (Offsite-box 947, Folder 5-7)
  - Grant, Ulysses Simpson: Sketches, 1929-1993, undated (Offsite-box 947, Folder 8-13)
  - Hayes, Rutherford Birchard, 1930-1940, 1947-1991, undated (Offsite-box 947, Folder 14-15)
  - Hayes, Mrs. Rutherford Birchard (née Lucy Ware Webb), 1940-1946, 1960-1968, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 948, Folder 1)
  - Garfield, James Abram: Sketches, 1931-1992 (Offsite-box 948, Folder 2-4)
  - Arthur, Chester Alan, 1934-1993 (Offsite-box 948, Folder 5-6)
  - Cleveland, Grover: Sketches, 1930-1993 (Offsite-box 948, Folder 7-11)
  - McKinley, William: Sketches, 1930-1993 (Offsite-box 948, Folder 12-15)
  - McKinley, Mrs. William (née Ida Saxton), 1964-1968, 1980 (Offsite-box 948, Folder 16)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore: Sketches, 1958-1986 (Offsite-box 811, Folder 4-17)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore: Sketches, 1929-1960 (Offsite-box 812, Folder 1-5)
  - Wilson, Woodrow: Sketches, 1944-1981 (Offsite-box 812, Folder 6-17)
  - Wilson, Woodrow: Sketches, 1923-1943 (Offsite-box 813, Folder 1-2)
  - Wilson, Mrs. Woodrow (née Ellen Louise Axson), 1962-1965, 1971, 1981 (Offsite-box 813, Folder 3)
  - Harding, Warren Gamaliel: Sketches, 1930-1992 (Offsite-box 813, Folder 4-8)
  - Coolidge, Calvin: General, 1925-1933 (Offsite-box 813, Folder 9)
    This file contains two pieces of microfiche containing copies of an article from the New York Times from January 18, 1925 detailing a speech Coolidge gave to the American Society of Newspaper Editors.
  - Coolidge, Calvin: Sketches, 1952-1993 (Offsite-box 813, Folder 10-15)
  - Hoover, Herbert: General, 1948-1965 (Offsite-box 984, Folder 1-7)
  - Hoover, Herbert: General, 1925-1947 (Offsite-box 813, Folder 16-19)
  - Hoover, Herbert: Sketches, 1983-1993 (Offsite-box 984, Folder 8)
  - Hoover, Herbert: Sketches, 1962-1982 (Offsite-box 814, Folder 1-7)
  - Hoover, Herbert: Sketches, 1926-1961 (Offsite-box 984, Folder 9-15)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Administration, 1939-1993 (Offsite-box 984, Folder 16-18)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Administration, 1930-1939 (Offsite-box 985, Folder 1)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Advertising, 1935-1938, 1949, 1966-1970 (Offsite-box 985, Folder 2)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Advisers and Assistants, 1932-1948, 1955-1990, undated (Offsite-box 985, Folder 3-5)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Agriculture, 1932-1944, 1960-1965 (Offsite-box 985, Folder 6)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Appointments, 1935-1945, 1961-1986 (Offsite-box 985, Folder 7)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Archives, 1938-1993 (Offsite-box 985, Folder 8-10)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Awards and Honors, 1932-1986 (Offsite-box 985, Folder 11-14)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Books, etc. (About), 1970-1993 (Offsite-box 985, Folder 15-17)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Books, etc. (About), 1932-1969 (Offsite-box 986, Folder 1-8)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Books, etc. (By), 1930-1950, 1964-1972, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 986, Folder 9)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Budget, 1934-1945, 1956, 1963-1968 (Offsite-box 986, Folder 10-11)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Business, 1934-1953, 1960-1965 (Offsite-box 986, Folder 12-13)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Business: A-Z, 1930-1945, 1955-1970, 1982-1983, undated (Offsite-box 986, Folder 14)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Cabinet, 1933-1948, 1955-1990 (Offsite-box 986, Folder 15-16)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Cartoons, 1932-1946, 1959-1967, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 986, Folder 17)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Characteristics, 1934-1993 (Offsite-box 986, Folder 18-19)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Civil Defense, 1944 (Offsite-box 814, Folder 8)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Civil Rights, 1932-1970 (Offsite-box 814, Folder 9)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Clothing, 1933-1982 (Offsite-box 814, Folder 10)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Clubs and Societies, 1932-1947, 1953, 1961-1967, undated (Offsite-box 814, Folder 11)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Communism, 1936-1970 (Offsite-box 814, Folder 12)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Conferences, 1933-1970 (Offsite-box 814, Folder 13-16)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Congress, 1934-1992 (Offsite-box 814, Folder 17-19)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Correspondence, 1930-1987 (Offsite-box 814, Folder 20-21)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Crime, 1930-1945, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 814, Folder 22)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Disarmament, 1933, 1951 (Offsite-box 814, Folder 23)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Domestic, 1964, 1971-1992 (Offsite-box 814, Folder 24-25)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Domestic Affairs: A-Z, 1934-1945, 1959-1968 (Offsite-box 815, Folder 1)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Economy, 1932-1970 (Offsite-box 815, Folder 2-3)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Education, 1936-1943, 1970 (Offsite-box 815, Folder 4)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Family, 1931-1952, 1959-1991 (Offsite-box 815, Folder 5)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Fiscal, 1931-1944, 1960-1967 (Offsite-box 815, Folder 8-9)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign, 1971-1993 (Offsite-box 815, Folder 10-11)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Finances (Personal), 1932-1953, 1962-1971 (Offsite-box 815, Folder 6-7)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Aid, 1940-1944, 1961-1966 (Offsite-box 815, Folder 12)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations, 1932-1970 (Offsite-box 815, Folder 13-18)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations: A-Z, 1933-1946, 1952-1969 (Offsite-box 815, Folder 19)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations: Argentina, 1939-1946, 1958-1964 (Offsite-box 815, Folder 20)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations: Brazil, 1940-1945, 1960, 1966 (Offsite-box 815, Folder 21)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations: Canada, 1936-1951, 1960-1966 (Offsite-box 815, Folder 22)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations: China, 1937-1945, 1952-1969, undated (Offsite-box 815, Folder 23)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations: France, 1939-1945, 1951, 1959-1970, undated (Offsite-box 815, Folder 24-25)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations: Germany, 1943-1948, 1955, 1961-1970 (Offsite-box 815, Folder 26)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations: Germany, 1934-1942 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 1)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations: Great Britain, 1934-1970 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 2-4)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations: Greece, 1941-1942 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 5)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations: Italy, 1937-1945, 1955-1957 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 6)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations: Japan, 1932-1970 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 7-8)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations: Mexico, 1933-1942, 1960-1962 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 9)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations: Morocco, 1942, 1951-1957, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 10)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations: Philippines, 1934-1935, 1941-1945, 1955 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 11)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations: Poland, 1932, 1939-1945, 1955, 1961-1970 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 12)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations: Puerto Rico, 1937, 1943-1946, 1965 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 13)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations: Saudi Arabia, 1945-1949 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 14)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Foreign Relations: Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1933-1970 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 15-17)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Friends, 1932-1987 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 18)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Gifts, 1933-1955, 1964, 1975 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 19)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Health, 1950-1986, 1992 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 20)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Health (Personal), 1928-1949, 1972 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 21)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Housing and Urban Renewal, 1937, 1942, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 22)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Inauguration, 1931-1945, 1960-1968, 1974-1989, undated (Offsite-box 816, Folder 23-24)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Jokes and Skits, 1933-1951, 1958-1970, 1976-1981, 1987 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 25)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Judicial, 1934-1970 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 26-27)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Labor, 1932-1946, 1954-1970 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 28-29)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Labor: A-Z, 1933-1944, 1959-1968 (Offsite-box 816, Folder 30)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Military, 1933-1947, 1953-1970 (Offsite-box 817, Folder 1-4)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Monuments and Sculptures, 1936-1992 (Offsite-box 817, Folder 5-8)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Names, 1937-1952, 1961-1966, 1979-1982, 1992 (Offsite-box 817, Folder 9)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Natural Resources, 1931-1944, 1954, 1960-1970 (Offsite-box 817, Folder 10-11)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Nuclear, 1943-1945, 1954-1966 (Offsite-box 817, Folder 12)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Pets, 1933-1934, 1941-1952, 1960-1964, 1972-1974, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 817, Folder 13)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Pictures (of), 1932-1987, 1993 (Offsite-box 817, Folder 14-15)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Politics, 1940-1993 (Offsite-box 817, Folder 16-23)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Politics, 1930-1939 (Offsite-box 827, Folder 1-3)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Polls, 1934-1962, 1979-1982, 1992 (Offsite-box 827, Folder 4)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Possessions, 1941-1943, 1951, 1957-1964, 1981 (Offsite-box 827, Folder 5)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Powers and Duties, 1932-1944, 1959-1988 (Offsite-box 827, Folder 6)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Press Conferences, 1934-1945, 1952, 1967-1973, 1979-1988 (Offsite-box 827, Folder 7-8)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Press Relations, 1931-1988, undated (Offsite-box 827, Folder 9-14)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Public Health, 1944-1945, 1960, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 827, Folder 15)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Public Works, 1935-1944, 1963-1966 (Offsite-box 827, Folder 16)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Quotes, 1932-1992 (Offsite-box 827, Folder 17-19)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Recreation, 1941-1945, 1961-1982 (Offsite-box 827, Folder 20)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Recreation: A-Z [IN CONSERVATION], undated (Offsite-box 827, Folder 21)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Recreation: Art, 1939-1942, 1956, 1962-1967, 1982-1987 (Offsite-box 827, Folder 22)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Recreation: Baseball, 1936-1942, 1955, 1966, 1975 (Offsite-box 828, Folder 1)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Recreation: Fishing, 1934-1944, 1967 (Offsite-box 828, Folder 2)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Recreation: Music, 1935-1938, 1945-1946, 1961-1963, 1979 (Offsite-box 828, Folder 3)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Recreation: Reading [IN CONSERVATION BOX], 1934-1955, 1961-1973, undated (Offsite-box 828, Folder 4)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Recreation: Sailing and Swimming, 1932-1942, 1951-1964 (Offsite-box 828, Folder 5)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Recreation: Stamps, 1933-1947, 1954, 1961-1970, undated (Offsite-box 828, Folder 6)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Recreation: Theater, 1934-1938, 1959, 1962-1970, 1978 (Offsite-box 828, Folder 7)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Religion, 1931-1970, 1978-1983, undated (Offsite-box 828, Folder 8)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Residences [1964 IS IN CONSERVATION], 1932-1964 (Offsite-box 828, Folder 9-12)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Science, 1961-1963 (Offsite-box 828, Folder 13)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Security (Personal), 1933-1943, 1950, 1956-1970, 1981-1985, undated (Offsite-box 828, Folder 14-15)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Sketches [1982 IS IN CONSERVATION], 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 828, Folder 16-20)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Sketches, 1940-1981 (Offsite-box 829, Folder 1-8)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Social, 1934-1939, 1944, 1965-1969, 1978 (Offsite-box 829, Folder 9)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Speeches [1941 IS IN CONSERVATION], 1940-1948, 1960-1992 (Offsite-box 829, Folder 10-15)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Speeches, 1930-1939 (Offsite-box 830, Folder 1-6)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Speeches and Diction, 1933-1948, 1956-1968, 1976-1989 (Offsite-box 830, Folder 7-8)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Staff, 1933-1945, 1961-1972, 1979-1983, undated (Offsite-box 830, Folder 9)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: State of the Union, 1934-1945, 1968, 1978 (Offsite-box 830, Folder 10-11)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Taxes, 1931-1944, 1962-1968 (Offsite-box 830, Folder 12)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Trade, 1940-1945, 1960-1962 (Offsite-box 830, Folder 13)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Transport, 1932-1970, undated (Offsite-box 830, Folder 14)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Travel, 1931-1945, 1955-1963, 1972-1978, 1984 (Offsite-box 830, Folder 15-16)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: United Nations, 1942-1948, 1954-1955, 1961-1965 (Offsite-box 830, Folder 17)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Visitors, 1939-1943, 1960-1962, 1969, 1982, 1989 (Offsite-box 831, Folder 1)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Welfare, 1933-1945, 1960-1968 (Offsite-box 831, Folder 2)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Youth, 1940-1944 (Offsite-box 831, Folder 3)
  - Truman, Harry S.: General, 1934-1973 (Offsite-box 831, Folder 4-18)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Administration, 1944, 1951-1992 (Offsite-box 831, Folder 19-21)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Administration, 1938-1949 (Offsite-box 832, Folder 1-3)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Advertising, 1944 (Offsite-box 832, Folder 4)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Advisers and Assistants, 1945-1983 (Offsite-box 832, Folder 5-8)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Agriculture, 1945-1967 (Offsite-box 832, Folder 9)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Appointments, 1945-1952, 1958-1961, 1972-1990 (Offsite-box 832, Folder 10-15)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Archives, 1950-1992 (Offsite-box 832, Folder 16-17)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Awards and Honors, 1950-1985 (Offsite-box 832, Folder 18-20)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Awards and Honors, 1945-1949 (Offsite-box 833, Folder 1)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Books, etc. (About), 1945-1992, undated (Offsite-box 833, Folder 2-4)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Books, etc. (By), 1944-1945, 1952-1966, 1972-1993 (Offsite-box 833, Folder 5-8)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Budget, 1945-1964 (Offsite-box 833, Folder 9-12)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Business, 1947-1952, 1961-1967 (Offsite-box 833, Folder 13-14)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Business, 1937-1970 (Offsite-box 833, Folder 15-18)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Cabinet, 1950-1985 (Offsite-box 833, Folder 19-21)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Cabinet, 1945-1949 (Offsite-box 834, Folder 1-2)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Cartoons, 1945-1956, 1963-1967, 1978-1983 (Offsite-box 834, Folder 3)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Characteristics, 1944-1985, 1992-1993, undated (Offsite-box 834, Folder 4-5)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Civil Defense, 1950-1952, 1962 (Offsite-box 834, Folder 6)
  - Truman, Harry S.: Civil Rights, 1948-1970 (Offsite-box 834, Folder 7-9)